Previously on Smallville.
Who are you?
Lois Lane.
I think we are going to enjoy a long and fruitful partnership, Miss Sullivan.
I need your help.
Your father murdered his parents.
There's no proof.
Only the voicemail confession of Lionel Luther himself.
I'm leaving.
Paris.
Lionel Luther, you're under arrest for murder.
Poor Kent is dead.
I don't believe that safe house explosion was an accident.
She's dead as a result of her own actions.
I had nothing to do with it.
I promise I will find out who did this to you.
You're not the only one who misses her.
I'm just the only one doing something about it.
Lois?
Chloe's still alive.
I know you find it hard to believe, but trust me.
Chloe's not buried in that grave.
How do you know that?
Look, I want her back more than anyone,
but don't you think your hunch is a rung on the whole grief ladder?
None of this would have happened if I'd have been there.
OK, Commando.
I don't get you.
Half the time, you're all meek, yes, ma, yes, pa.
And the other half, you are the most overconfident guy
you've ever met.
Doesn't happen to you much, does it?
Not being able to peg someone right away?
Oh, get over yourself.
You are not that complicated.
This is Chloe's safe house.
You mean what's left?
What's left of it.
Oh, my god, Chloe.
What did they do to you?
What exactly do you expect to find here?
I don't know, but the FBI sealed the case.
Even the autopsy reports.
Doesn't that sound a little odd?
Remind me if I'm ever a witness not
to put my life in the hands of the FBI.
Maybe she got out before the explosion.
They said she walked inside, Clark.
I don't know how anyone could survive this.
Look, you may be in denial thinking Chloe's alive,
but I'm going to find out who did this to her.
Let's get out of here, Clark.
This place gives me the creeps.
Are you crazy?
I am.
Tell me you just found out.
Seлох the
People in the Saudi Arabia
are all 보니까.
How do you want that to change for you?
Sounds reasonable, but I don't like it to be very normal.
Hey, watch out!
Get out of here.
Now do you know what?
I yanked out from this car.
I don't have time to complain!
Get explore!
In a hurry?
Take me out!
Go get it!
Oh!
Lois!
Don't just stand there. Come on.
Relax, sir.
Find them. Get them.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Yeah.
Come on.
That's unlike a little north-by-northwest action
to get the blood pumping, huh?
Um...
We usually take turns in the bathroom.
Oh, don't start with me, Smallville.
You're the one taking the marathon shower.
Besides, my delicate feminine sensibilities
weren't offended the first time I got a glimpse of you,
Clark Junior.
My parents kind of missed the whole Woodstock phase.
Besides, they freaked out the last time
they caught me in a co-ed situation.
Last time?
So, the Eagle Scout does have a few secrets in the closet.
Just forget it, all right?
That's my shirt.
It's the only thing I could find that was clean.
Hey, let's keep this morning's game of chopper tag a secret.
Okay.
Right.
Because I'm the one who can't keep my mouth shut.
Mom.
Hi.
You're home.
Hi, Mrs. Kent.
Oh, Dad.
How are you?
Hey, Dad.
I'm fine.
How are you?
You?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Okay.
You're going to the hospital, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I think I'll go now.
I don't know if it's a good idea to take your dad with you.
I don't know.
I've been thinking of getting a job.
I've been thinking about going into a job.
I don't know if I have time.
Well, I don't know.
I can't wait.
I don't understand what the big deal is here.
We just took a shower.
Showers? We took separate showers.
At noon.
We were just gonna...
We went to Chloe's safe house.
These guys showed up and chased us.
Into a field and there was all this dirt.
Clark.
That is a federal crime scene.
And the last thing that we want is for you two kids to get involved with the FBI.
Whoever it was, we don't need to worry
because their chopper is face first in the middle of the field.
Your nonverbals are killing me and...
This seems like it's a family matter, so...
I'm just gonna get out of the way.
Way to go.
Please tell me that you did not crash that helicopter.
Waste of a new suit, isn't it, Dad?
I don't think so, son.
Even if Miss Sullivan were alive and testified against me,
you and I both know that the jury would still find me not guilty.
But I am sorry, Lex.
Sorry that you killed a bright young woman just because she stood in your way.
My apology concerns you and me.
I'm sorry that you couldn't foresee the consequences of your actions when you betrayed me.
You can save the threats, Dad.
I'm not as easy a target as you seem to think.
All those tests, all those trials have made you strong.
But this time it's different.
You'll never know when it will happen, but it will happen.
Each swallow of wine you take,
every key you turn,
every friend,
every moment you make,
you'll never have another moment's peace.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mmm.
You look good.
I'm just sure about you now.
You look great.
Thank you.
Hey.
So, from your message I didn't quite get if this is a stop over or if you're back for good.
For a while,
I guess Paris just wasn't for me.
Yeah.
museums, late-night jazz clubs, walks along the scent.
I could see how that could all get boring.
Let's just say that I felt as though something was calling me out.
A little cryptic, but I'll take it.
You picked a good day for a homecoming.
You know, Clark just resurfaced, too.
Interesting timing.
Funny, I don't remember asking about Clark.
Actually, I came by because I saw the Talon was boarded up.
Thought you would have sold it by now.
Yeah, well, I had a little trouble letting it go.
What, are you in the market for a partner?
No.
No, I want to rent the apartment.
I was just just paying attention to hours ago, Thinking back to, like, your demo session,
Is there any chance I would have owned a house somewhere else?
Ugh.
Okay.
You lost an acres.
What, I didn't buy yourself a house?
It's best to leave Taylor down to you just because Facebook makes a fool of his business.
Come on, I don't want any more money.
Forget it.
I hope the clerk is right.
Otherwise, this is going to be really ugly, Chloe.
Okay.
He's right.
Where's Chloe Sullivan?
Who the hell are you?
You'd better tell me where she is.
What?
You're stuck here if you don't talk.
Posse couldn't get to me the first time,
so the bar sent you.
You can both kiss my ass.
NOOOOO!!!
hehe
HE'S BUNKY!
ET
Aassee
ۂ
ooh
Aерш
ae
ogh
ʀɸ
h leg
oglass
It fell between us.
He's really naked.
Ugh, shut it...
Oh f Tact 쉬
story
He's zero on drugs.
period
dog
sé
I had a р poor dog he came to target me with.
I don't know why he kick and feed me, so he's like a cat dog.
Anyway, look there's fucking body there alive man.
mm
n.n
Are you okay?
Where the hell did he go?
Medieval psychopath?
Guess you'd have to be in order to dig up a grave
in the middle of the day.
Actually, that was me.
It's my cousin's grave.
Lois Lane.
Lana Lang.
Lana.
You're back.
Hi. Hi, Clark.
Lois.
How did you two...
We just met.
I stopped by the cemetery to pay my respects to Chloe.
I think you're forgetting about the part where you saved my life.
Some guincy boy came after us at Chloe's grave.
Look, Clark, if you really think...
If you really think...
If you really think that Chloe's alive,
I want to help find her.
Um, Lana,
look, I don't want to get your hopes up,
but we don't know anything for sure.
Okay.
You're back from Paris.
You must have found what you were looking for.
I'll say.
Who wouldn't want a hot summer fling
in the most romantic city on Earth?
I was going to tell you.
It's okay.
Really?
You too.
We never...
Not really.
...had a thing.
It's complicated.
A complicated thing.
Never mind.
Well, um, I'm going to go.
Oh.
The awkward tension's just getting started.
I'm a little distracted.
I'm going to call you.
I only came in because I wanted to.
Early crashed and burned on that one.
Must be a daily ritual for you.
Only when I'm barreling into a train wreck.
Listen to me.
I really think we're onto something here.
I did my research,
and it's not working.
it turns out Luther Corp paid for Chloe's funeral.
Why would they do that? It doesn't make any sense.
I guess the real question to ask would be,
why would somebody bury an empty casket for nothing?
Right, Clark?
Clark?
Wow.
She didn't take any prisoners, did she?
Lana?
Cute, smart.
Gutsy.
And way too much for you to handle.
I can see why you're in love with her.
Look, you're really not the person I want to talk to about this.
Sit yourself.
It's just...
I knew she'd be digging out of the people.
What?
You still don't understand how you could...
feel like you know someone so completely.
Like, you know everything about them, and then just all of a sudden...
You don't even know what continent they're on.
Do you always have to finish people's thoughts?
Well, am I right?
What?
Come on!
We gotta go!
Come on,boarding.
We've gotta go.
somebody's got to see her.
Hey.
westernум
Come after me.
Hey.
Where are you going now?
Yeah, at home.
Your though it.
Well, I'm going.
Get out of there, Jack.
グ می
I want to go.
Are you going to Hulu?
No.
You stay here.
To keep an eye on me, is that it, boss?
Drop it, though.
Why? I'm obviously on to something here.
You wouldn't be calling out the birds if I was late for dinner.
You didn't seriously invite him to dinner.
Clark, Mr. Lane is a three-star general.
I think he deserves a little respect.
Mom. Mom.
This is some place you got here, Mr. and Mrs. Kent.
And again, I'd like to thank you for keeping an eye on my little Lo.
Can I offer you a Shavello?
Hand-rolled with some of the finest tobacco in the U.S. of A.
No, I, uh... My heart isn't exactly what it used to be.
I'm gonna have to take a rain check on your hospitality, Mrs. Kent.
You're welcome any time.
Well, thank you. Let's double-time it, Lo.
This is about Chloe.
Clark, find the connection to Luther Corp.
Good night, Doc.
Good night.
I was assigned to the accident in Jakarta, and the shuttle disaster.
Impressive.
And maybe you could help explain to me how a door rips off a jet at 20,000 feet.
We found no traces of explosive residue.
Now, all evidence suggests that the door was extricated from outside the aircraft by a manual force.
I'm sorry. Are you trying to tell me someone did this from outside my plane?
Agent Stocker, will you excuse us?
Does this mean you're talking to me again?
Only because I don't have a choice.
Relegated from friend to last resort.
Guess I'll have to accept it if it's my only chance to prove myself.
Good. Because I want you to help me find Chloe.
Look, I'd like to set things straight between us, Clark, but...
Don't you think raising someone from the grave is setting the bar a little high?
Lex, Chloe's not in her grave.
She was a lynchpin in your father's trial.
You would have had investigators crawling all over that area.
What'd they find?
I pulled some strings and asked the FBI not to release all the morbid details.
The fact is, that explosion took out an entire...
I'm sorry.
...acre, and the reason Chloe's casket is empty is...
...it's because there wasn't anything left.
I'm sorry, Clark.
Just keep going, okay.
What's the matter?
Kevin must've escaped when he came to the Lighthouse.
If we look in there, we'll see if you've broadened your view, but other than that...
Michael?
I'm sorry to say, I was looking at the monsters' antics and wanted to complete
the investigation right away.
The Nirvana Cips are un Almost there.
You keep talking, didn't you?
A long time ago, I probably pulled this wonderful bucket.
Of course not.
It may already have shown us through to a fire.
This probably might be consistent with this been here on Kiten Switch.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Chloe never made it to the witness stand.
The only thing I could do was beat him to it.
The house was built on tunnels
left from the Underground Railroad.
Seconds after Chloe and her dad entered,
we rushed them underneath the house.
The explosion was rigged to cave in the tunnel behind them.
The cops never found it.
And Sam Lane?
I didn't trust the FBI.
I needed someone who could engineer the rescue.
She's at the old foundry.
Don't worry, Clark.
I'll have people over there in minutes.
Get me General Lane.
I'll be right back.
The truth is, he's been lying to me from day one.
The legend on the cave wall says I'm destined to have an enemy.
All this time I've been worried about Lionel.
But I'm beginning to think that the real threat
was right in front of me.
I think it's Lex.
Come on, так!
L 라는.
What are you doing down here?
Probably the same thing you are.
It was peaceful...
Lana.
You're two for two.
You keep showing up when I least expect to see you.
I'm not trying to surprise you, Clark.
I know.
It's just, when you left, I...
What's wrong?
I wasn't sure when I'd see you again.
It's funny, isn't it?
After everything we've been through.
I thought it would take us longer to get over it.
Us?
Yeah, you and Lois.
Lois?
She's bossy.
She's stuck up. She's rude.
I can't stand her.
The best ones always start that way.
Do you believe in destiny?
I don't want to.
But you can't escape it, can you?
Even if you don't know what it is yet?
Lana, what is it you're not telling me?
Does it have something to do with this guy you met?
No. No. Um, no it doesn't.
But I'm sorry that you found out the way you did.
I should go.
I just finally found out.
And I'm not sure why you are.
Go.
Oh, he's alive.
Relax, TJ.
He'll get better.
What's wrong?
No.
But wasn't it you who warned me,
don't wound what you cannot kill?
Oh, and Dad...
I wouldn't have missed this for the world.
Er...
Hi.
I'm freaking you out with the whole Cary Grant moment, aren't I?
What are you doing here?
Giving you time.
You're beautiful.
I, uh, found this.
Jason and I had to go back home.
I wish I had time to explain.
So now you do.
I'm sorry, Jason.
I, uh...
I don't know what to say.
It's okay.
It's all right.
You know, I kept trying to convince myself that this wasn't about me,
but...
You can't really put that in a note, can you?
Come on.
Wait.
Jason, I'm not sorry to see you.
You know, it's just...
You came all this way, and I just...
I wish that I had a better explanation for you.
For why you left Paris or why you left me?
You know how I feel about you.
That hasn't changed.
But I can't go back.
Lana, I didn't come here to get you.
I came here to be with you.
She will be loved.
She will.
And I'm in love.
I'm sorry.